Austin Peavey

(404)642-3610 - Apeavey10@gmail.com - www.linkedin.com/in/austin-peavey

SUMMARY

Advanced training in software engineering and hardware fabrication, collaborating with fortune 500 companies such as Boeing and SAIC to develop virtual training simulators and environments. Three years of applied training in programming languages such as C++ and CS-Script with a heavy emphasis on VR technologies and game development. Completed B.S. degree in Visualization and Simulation in 2.5 years.

OBJECTIVE

Seeking to use extensive knowledge of advanced computer systems in an entry-level position to help optimize and advance the agenda and profitability of a technology company utilizing these systems.

RELEVANT COMPUTER SKILLS

Software

- Compilers: Visual Studios, Mono Develop, Arduino IDE, MineCraft ComputerCraft Mod, Spyder, RoboCode, Windows Command Line, Linux Command Line.
- Operating Systems: Microsoft Windows 7, Windows 10, Linux.
- Modeling: SolidWorks, Maya basics.
- Libraries: SteamVR, Oculus VR, Vurtuix Omni, DirectX 11, Adafruit.
- Applied use of programing languages including C, C++, C#, Java, Python, Lua, JSON, HTML/CSS, Windws and Linux bash files.

RELEVANT PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Embedded Systems Programmer - Full Sail University - Stewart Platform Assembly

3/2017 - 5/2017

- SolidWorks solid part modeling with assembly.
- Fabrication using 3D printer, LPKF, laser cutter, and lathe.
- C++ programing for Inverse kinematic for 6DOF platform motion.

Software Engineer - Full Sail University - VR Maintenance Simulation

7/2017 - 8/2017

- Implementation of a mechanic of my design for interacting with items in virtual reality.
- Shown at SAIC's booth at I/ITSEC.
- Unity scripting and bug fixing with Steam VR integration.

Experience Engineer Intern - Boeing - Simulation Engineer

10/2017 - 2/2018

- Hardware Fabrication to attach to MOOG 6 DOF motion platform.
- Experience design for Boeing 737-800 Scenario Based Training.
- Hands on training of UDP packet structure for MOOG 6 DOF motion platform.

EDUCATION

Full Sail University

2/2015 - 11/2017

Winter Park. Florida

Simulation and Visualization – Bachelors of Science

Courses include: Object Oriented Programing, Data Structures, Software Engineering, Networking,

Operating Systems, Microcontrollers, Virtual and Augmented Reality, Digital Fabrication, Artificial

Intelligence, Graphics, Data Visualization and Modeling